Anggriawan Rayzadmiko

Bogor Regency, West Java | +6281310008091 | anggriawan.net@gmail.com | https://razd-net.vercel.app

Summary

A fresh graduate in System and Instrumentation Physics, who has great interest in IoT and website development. Also known as hard-working college student which loves to solving problem, troubleshooting, and have great attention of detail. Have experienced in embedded C programming and Next.js framework.

Experience

Erlangga

Freelance - Motion Graphic

Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- · Created animation video using Adobe After Effects
- Created assets for the animation
- Responsible for video quality according to client requests

BRIN

Research Assistant

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

- Modeled and developed a PID controller using Raspberry Pi programmed with Python and tuning it, achieve a very stable response on rocket flight
- Modeled and developed a control system for rocket VTOL that achive miss distance less than 1 meter on simulation
- Suggested the controller algorithm method
- Assisted in a journal writing

Exedu Start-Up Project

UI Designer

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022

- Designed a google based website (Google Sites) that have more than 1500 users
- Created a website prototype in Figma and collaborated with Product Manager
- Collaborated with content writer to maximize the UI design according to the content, achieve a responsive web across any platform
- Designed attractive content design to reach the public in instagram

Universitas Indonesia

Control System Laboratory Assistant

Feb - Jul 2022

- Evaluated practitioner's competence in the form of a presentation
- Trained practitioners about control theory in practice with microcontroller and data acquisition software

Lembaga Penerbangan dan Antariksa Negara (LAPAN)

Research Intern

Jul - Sept 2021

Graduated: Jul 2022

- Built a PID controller with LabVIEW and implement it on rocket flight guidance and VTOL, resulting miss distance less than 1 meter on simulation
- Reported the progress and method of the controller algorithm

Education

Universitas Indonesia

Bachelor of Science – Physics – Instrumentation Physics GPA 3.51/4.00

- 3.51/4.00
 Thesis Research: Design of Cold Probe Temperature Controller on
- Thermoelectric Material Characterization System using Microcontroller
 Digital Signal Processing Project: Speech Recognition Based on Mel Spectrogram with Deep Learning using MATLAB and Python
- Sensors and Actuators Project: Design and Build Vehicle Noise Test System for Two-Wheel Motor Vehicle

Technical Skills

Arduino | Python | Embedded C | HTML5/CSS3 | JavaScript | React | Next.js | MongoDB | MySQL

Organization and Volunteer

Physics Department Student Association

Staff

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

Designed attractive content to reach the public in instagram and students

Pesta Rakyat Fisika (PRF)
Staff of Quiz Competition at Elementary School Level
Designed attractive and interactive question with PowerPoint

Jan - Februari 2020